Some stay for a night. Some stay for a week. Some never leave.
Barbarian is a horror, thriller film directed by Zach Cregger.
In town for a job interview, a young woman arrives at her Airbnb late at night only to find that
it has been mistakenly double-booked and a strange man is already staying there.
Against her better judgement, she decides to stay the night anyway.
Tess, played by Georgina Campbell.
AJ, played by Justin Long.
Keith, played by Bill Skarsgård.
Frank, played by Richard Brake.
The Mother, played by Matthew Patrick Davis.
Andre, played by Jaymes Butler.
Barbarian is a 2022 American horror film written and directed by Zach
Cregger in his solo screenwriting and directorial debut.
It is produced by Arnon Milchan, Roy Lee, Raphael Margules, and J.
The film stars Georgina Campbell, Bill Skarsgård, and Justin Long.
The story follows a woman who rents a house on Airbnb
and discovers a dark secret inside.
Barbarian premiered at San Diego Comic-Con on July 22, 2022, and was theatrically
released in the United States on September 9, 2022, by 20th Century Studios.
The film received positive reviews from critics and grossed $45
million worldwide against a budget of about $4 million.
The film explores themes of monster, sexual
abuse, paranoia, flashback, basement.
The tone is dark and intense.